program that can be used as a guessing game. The game is played by Dealer and Player. Dealer generates a random integer number between 0 and 10. Player has to guess it. The program should take input from Player as long as Player inputs same number as Dealer’s input was. Player gets advice to choose greater or smaller numbers in next choice. Finally, program has to also display the number of tries until the number is guessed. Program operates as follow: Player: 2 Try a greater number. Player: 7 Try a smaller number. Player: 5 That’s right! Number of tries: 3 Hint: import random and generate random numbers by using random.randint() in the desired range
